How close can you get to a killer before you're too close?
Under Suspicion is a crime, thriller film directed by Simon Moore.
In the late 1950s, British police officer Tony Aaron resigns from the force after
sleeping with Hazel, wife of the man whose house he was supposed to guard.
In his new job as a fake private investigator, he helps couples get divorces
by photographing Hazel having "affairs" with the husband.
When she is murdered during a job, Tony begins having an affair with the dead
man's mistress, Angeline, while trying to prove his innocence.
Tony Aaron, played by Liam Neeson.
Angeline, played by Laura San Giacomo.
Frank Vance, played by Kenneth Cranham.
Selina, played by Alphonsia Emmanuel.
Hazel Aaron, played by Maggie O'Neill.
Roscoe, played by Stephen Moore.
Under Suspicion is a 1991 neo noir erotic thriller film directed by
Simon Moore and starring Liam Neeson and Laura San Giacomo.
Neeson won best actor at the 1992 Festival du Film
Policier de Cognac for his performance.
The film explores themes of hotel room, adultery,
brighton, england, divorce, private detective.
The tone is intense.